AMAN CHOUBEY (Digital & Influencer Marketing)

E-Mail: bhrigumana@gmail.com

Contact: +91 9340 725 987

LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/2ac2

Summary

With an entrepreneur mindset. I am a successful Digital marketing strategist and Influencer Marketing expert. I have successful client's business with good digital presence and reach in Indian Market. You'll get a clear understanding of the underlying principles behind digital marketing, how it works, and how you can use it to create a competitive advantage for your business. I work on Proven ROI's.

Clients Handled:

- https://www.houseplansdaily.com/
- http://bhriguvastu.in/
- https://vastulogic.co.in/

Skills

- Digital Marketing Innovations
- Digital Marketing Channels
- Digital Marketing Analytics
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- Search Engine Marketing (SEM)
- Influencer Marketing
- Google Analytics
- Google Ads
- Email Marketing

Experience

Affiliate Marketing Manager

BGD Tech Pvt Limited

Oct 2022 – Present (4 mos & present)

Working as a Influencer/ Affiliate Manager. Product- 1win I have successfully collaborated with renowned Influencers for BGD Tech Pvt Ltd.



Blogger manager

DRIM

Jul 2022 – Oct 2022 (4 mos)

Worked as a Personal Blogger Manager. I have worked for Domino's India, Zepto, Melorra, Olymp Trade, IND Money, Olymp Trade CPA, AstroYogi CPI, HopScotch, Mc Delivery. I have successfully collaborated with renowned Influencers for DRIM.



Intern team Lead

JanakiBharath Software Solutions Pvt Ltd

Jul 2022 – Oct 2022 (4 mos)

Intern team lead managing team of Social media marketing, search engine optimization, content marketing & campaign management. Managing team of 11 colleagues. Work role: Allot tasks to each team. Clear doubts of team. Help them with latest information in digital marketing. Set up weekly meetings with CEO. Report directly to CEO. Manage and write MOM. Analyze and check all the works reports timely by team members.

Affiliate Marketing Specialist

https://www.linkmyy.com/Amanc123

May 2022 – Jul 2022 (3 mos)

Affiliate Network at Linkmyy _ ID _ https://www.linkmyy.com/Amanc123

Search Engine Optimization Specialist

Freelance

Jan 2020 – Jul 2022 (2 yrs 7 mos)

Grow your YouTube Channel with me. I am SEO and SEM expert and Specialist. I have successfully worked for my multiple clients with pretty good results in ROAS and ROI. SEO strategy for a website. A pre- set excel document is provided to you. There are 3 sections to this: keyword research, on page optimization, off page optimization.



Marketing Content Specialist

Self Employed

Jan 2022 – Jun 2022 (6 mos)

A Content Marketing plan was formulated for the Primary Digital Property based on the 3H (Hero, Hub, Hygiene) approach. A specific Hero content was also produced and published on the Primary Digital Property. Mama Earth



Social Media Marketing Specialist

Self Employed

Jan 2022 – Jun 2022 (6 mos)

The Project involved running outreach campaigns for primary digital property based on the requisite business requirement on Facebook or Instagram. The process to run the campaign was documented and the results and outcomes of the campaigns were analyzed. A report on the performance of the campaign was created.



Search Engine Marketing Specialist

Self Employed

Jan 2022 – Jun 2022 (6 mos)

Conducted competitive analysis and researched the keywords for personal digital property (website or blog) using Keyword Planner. Structured 3 campaigns on

Google Ads with relevant keywords and identified a relevant target audience to execute the campaigns to understand the audience's interest in the digital property. Compared the results with ads of competitors and reported the key learnings and recommendations from the analysis.

Wordpress Developer

Self Employed
Jan 2022 – Jun 2022 (6 mos)

Website Design using WordPress - PDP synopsis- Blue Print

1

Teaching Professional

Self Employed

Jan 2019 – Jun 2022 (3 yrs 6 mos)

I have trained several students as freelance and leverage their career in Digital Marketing. My expertise in SEO, SEM and Digital Marketing all Channels.

Vastu consultant and astrologer

Bhriguvastu

Apr 2018 – Apr 2022 (4 yrs 1 mo)

Founder & Managing Partner

MJ Architects & Constructions

Jan 2018 - Nov 2021 (3 yrs 11 mos)

WORKING on 2D AND 3D PROJECTS COMMERCIAL, RESIDENTIAL..

Vastu Consultant

https://mohanjyoti-architects-constructions.business.site/ Jan 2018 – Nov 2021 (3 yrs 11 mos)

Autocad Draftsman

Axis EPC Inc.

Dec 2018 (1 mo)

Autocad Draftsman.

Engineering Trainee

madhya pradesh public works department

Aug 2016 - Dec 2016 (5 mos)

Worked as a trainee engineer at Madhya Pradesh Public Works Department {MPPWD,Gwalior} in a Bridge Division duration 1/8/2016 till 12/12/2016.

Engineering Trainee

public health engineering department

Aug 2015 – Oct 2015 (3 mos)

Worked as a trainee engineer in Madhya Pradesh public health engineering department {MPPHED,Gwalior},there i learnt pipeline distribution work, water treatment at plant and supplying of water into the city duration 3/8/2015 till 5/10/2015.

9

Project Trainee

Dilip Buildcon Ltd.

Jun 2015 – Jul 2015 (2 mos)

Worked as a trainee engineer in a highway project at dilip buildcon pvt.ltd there i worked under a construction manager gained knowledge in flexible and rigid pavements, site work, lab work, surveying, estimation duration from 15/6/2015 till 15/7/2015.

Autocad Draftsman

Self employed

May 2013 – Jan 2015 (1 yr 9 mos)

Education

GREAT LAKE

Great Lakes Institute of Management

PGP - SDM, Digital Marketing

Jan 2022 – Aug 2022

POST GRADUATE PROGRAM IN STRATEGIC DIGITAL MARKETING The certificate below verifies that AMAN CHOUBEY has completed the POST GRADUATE PROGRAM IN STRATEGIC DIGITAL MARKETING

· A

Shree Maharshi College of Vedic Astrology

Postgraduate Degree, Vastu - Shastri Jan 2020 – Jan 2021

Per l

Shree Maharshi College of Vedic Astrology

Postgraduate Degree, Jyotish - Shastri Jan 2020 – Jan 2021

SAR

CADD Centre Training Services Private Limited

Proffessional in Architectural Design, Architecture 2018

ITM Group of Institutions

Bachelor's degree, Civil Engineering

St.pauls school , gwalior

Higher secondary

Licenses & certifications

trainee engineer at mppwd - madhya pradesh public works depatment.

Issued Aug 2016

Credential ID 2998



project trainee at dilip buildcon pvt ltd - Dilip Buildcon Ltd.

Issued Jun 2015

Credential ID U45201MP2006PLC018689

AutoCAD - Autodesk

Issued Jun 2016

CADD

Professional in Architectural Design - CADD Centre Chennai

Issued Mar 2017

Credential ID AC180366143

Madhya pradesh Public Health Engineering Department - MPHED, Gwalior Issued Oct 2015



Digital Marketing - DRIM

. **G**

Google Ads Search Certification - Google Digital Academy (Skillshop)

Issued Jul 2022 - Expires Jul 2023

Credential ID 120872556

G

Google Ads - Measurement Certification - Google Digital Academy (Skillshop)

Issued Jul 2022 - Expires Jul 2023

Credential ID 121021108

Œ

Google Ads Display Certification - Google Digital Academy (Skillshop)

Issued Jul 2022 – Expires Jul 2023

Credential ID 120220258



Google Ads Video Certification - Google Digital Academy (Skillshop)

Issued Jul 2022 – Expires Jul 2023

Credential ID 121029740

G

Shopping ads Certification - Google Digital Academy (Skillshop)

Issued Jul 2022 – Expires Jul 2023

Credential ID 121035338

G

Google Ads Apps Certification - Google Digital Academy (Skillshop)

Issued Jul 2022 – Expires Jul 2023

Credential ID 121075255

. **G**

Google Analytics Individual Qualification - Google Digital Academy (Skillshop)

Issued Jul 2022 – Expires Jul 2023

Credential ID 121076303

*

Email Marketing - HubSpot Academy

Issued Jul 2022 – Expires Aug 2024

Credential ID 617048ef712d4553bc4f176eafa0fb5b

2

Content Marketing - HubSpot Academy

Issued Jul 2022 - Expires Aug 2024

Credential ID 48fb2d53deae4ba1a4f539598221457f

G

Google Analytics 4 Certification - Google Digital Academy (Skillshop)

Issued Sep 2022 – Expires Sep 2023

Credential ID 125668616

K

Understanding the metaverse - KIMO Issued Aug 2022

K

Understanding the metaverse - KIMO Issued Aug 2022

e

Digital Business Models - Eventbrite

Issued Jul 2022

Google Ads Display Certification - Skillshop

Issued Jul 2022 – Expires Jul 2023 Credential ID 63221140

Google Ads Search Certification - Skillshop

Issued Jul 2022 – Expires Jul 2023 Credential ID 62890490

Google Ads Video Certification - Skillshop

Issued Jul 2022 – Expires Jul 2023 Credential ID 62992112

Google Ads Apps Certification - Skillshop

Issued Jul 2022 – Expires Jul 2023

Credential ID 63708118

Shopping ads Certification - Skillshop

Issued Jul 2022 – Expires Jul 2023

Credential ID 63484980

Hypnotherapy Practitioner - Mission Genius Mind Consultants (P) Limited